[
      { "answer": "parce que", "question": "weil" },
      { "answer": "du coup", "question": "folglich" },
      { "answer": "à cause de", "question": "deswegen" },
      { "answer": "mais", "question": "aber" },
      { "answer": "par contre", "question": "andererseits" },
      { "answer": "quand même", "question": "trotzdem" },
      { "answer": "au moins", "question": "mindestens" },
      { "answer": "d'ailleurs", "question": "übrigens" },
      { "answer": "en plus", "question": "außerdem" },
      { "answer": "aussi", "question": "auch" },
      { "answer": "alors", "question": "also" },
      { "answer": "voilà", "question": "da ist" },
      { "answer": "ici", "question": "hier" },
      { "answer": "là", "question": "da" },
      { "answer": "partout", "question": "überall" },
      { "answer": "près", "question": "nah" },
      { "answer": "lion", "question": "weit" },
      { "answer": "devant", "question": "vor" },
      { "answer": "derrière", "question": "hinten" },
      { "answer": "à gouche", "question": "links" },
      { "answer": "à droite", "question": "rechts" },
      { "answer": "à côte de", "question": "neben" },
      { "answer": "en face", "question": "gegenüber" },
      { "answer": "au bord de", "question": "am Ufer von" },
      { "answer": "sous", "question": "unter" },
      { "answer": "sur", "question": "über/auf" },
      { "answer": "un peu", "question": "ein bisschen" },
      { "answer": "très", "question": "sehr" },
      { "answer": "vraiment", "question": "wirklich" },
      { "answer": "beaucoup", "question": "viel" },
      { "answer": "trop", "question": "zu viel" },
      { "answer": "tout", "question": "alles" },
      { "answer": "bien sûr", "question": "natürlich" },
      { "answer": "d'abord", "question": "zunächst" },
      { "answer": "après", "question": "dann/dannach" },
      { "answer": "ensuite", "question": "schließlich" },
      { "answer": "et puis", "question": "und dann" },
      { "answer": "enfin", "question": "als Letztes/schließlich" },
      { "answer": "parfois", "question": "manchmal" },
      { "answer": "une semaine sur deux", "question": "jede zweite Woche" },
      { "answer": "le jeudi", "question": "Donnerstag" },
      { "answer": "souvent", "question": "alt" },
      { "answer": "toujours", "question": "immer" },
      { "answer": "depuis", "question": "seit" },
      { "answer": "tôt", "question": "früh" },
      { "answer": "tard", "question": "spät" },
      { "answer": "de ... à", "question": "von ... bis" },
      { "answer": "pendant", "question": "während" },
      { "answer": "avant", "question": "vor" },
      { "answer": "quand", "question": "wann" },
      { "answer": "hier", "question": "gestern" },
      { "answer": "maintenant", "question": "jetzt" },
      { "answer": "aujourd'hui", "question": "heute" },
      { "answer": "demain", "question": "morgen" },
      { "answer": "bientôt", "question": "bald" }
]   